



ALEJANDRO MARTÍN

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR

- alehamartinva@gmail.com
- +34 671 213 938
- https://alehaaaa.github.io/
- Berlin, Germany (originally Barcelona, Spain)

PROFILE

I am a 3D Character Animator with intuition and eye for detail. Experienced in production environments, receiving feedback from the Animation Director and Supervisor and collaborating with other Animators and the Rigging team, always pursuing a more efficient pipeline with custom Scripts and Tools.

I am excited to contribute to a production to grow with my team.

EDUCATION

EXPERIENCE

MASTER IN 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION

ECIB | 2021 - 2022

Lip-sync · Advanced Acting

DEGREE IN ANIMATION

ECIB | 2019 - 2021

2D · StopMotion · 3D

ACTING INTRODUCTION

Learned to embrace a character

EÒLIA THEATER SCHOOL 2021 - 2022

SKILLS

M AUTODESK MAYA



A ADOBE SUITE



English (C1, Advanced) Spanish (Native) Catalan (Native)

JUNIOR 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 3 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2023 - MAR 2024

Brought ideas and, through collaborative teamwork enhanced the animation with pipeline improvements and tool development.

- Animated a variety of animal characters, following references and learning about their anatomical behaviour.
- Specialized in animating Lip-syncs in German dialogues.
- Received feedback directly from the Animation Director.
- Team-worked to push the sequences to their best acting potential.
- Improved the animation pipeline with custom Tools and Scripts.

3D ANIMATOR FOR SHORT FILM BY VÍCTOR MARÍN ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | OCT 2022 - OCT 2023

Project currently in production, working side by side with the Director and Animation Supervisor, bringing ideas to the table.

- Animated and developed character traits, maintaining personalities throughout the story, with the tight guidance of the Supervisor.
- Recorded multiple references, based on the time frame and dialogs.
- Worked on a pose Library whilst animating to test the characters.
- Implemented a production pipeline to organize shots and files, created a variety of tools to streamline the animation process.
- Keeping deliveries according to the established production timeline, always open-minded to changes.